Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - E
        - Extra Strength - Can we all get along, 1993; SR-14301; Extra Strength (Box 273)
          Catalog # JOHN 8:12; A-side Matrix # JOHN 8:12-A
        - Exude - Boys just want to have sex, 1984; SR-14302; Exude (Box 273)
          Catalog # FF001; A-side Matrix # FF-001-A
          Feelin' Fine Records
        - E.Y.C. - Get some, 1993; SR-14303; E.Y.C. (Box 273)
          Catalog # GAS8P 2527; A-side Matrix # GAS 11604 FDS-1
        - E.Y.C. - Get some, 1993; SR-14304; E.Y.C. (Box 273)
        - E.Y.C. - Get some, 1993; SR-14305; E.Y.C. (Box 273)
          Catalog # GAS12-54605; A-side Matrix # GAS 11606 FDS-2
        - Ezee Posse - Love on love, 1989; SR-14306; Ezee Posse; Dr. Mouthquake (Box 273)
          Catalog # DMD 1473; A-side Matrix # STDM 58338 58339 58340-1